ABDULLAH AL NOMAN

UI/UX Engineer

Workspace Infotech Limited • +880-1682503304 • noman952362@gmail.com





ABOUT ME

As a Product Designer, interested in user problems, and finding solutions also responsible for designing and prototyping the user experience for a product. From inception to completion, he will oversee the entire process. Every chance he gets, he looks for an opportunity to use his skills and learn from others. User experience, improvement and problem-solving are his passions.

As well as being proficient in web design he is able to collaborate easily with developers. Passion, time, and attention are necessary for good things to flourish.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Workspace Infotech Limited

UI/UX ENGINEER (October 2021 – Present)

1 Year 4 Months

- Design mobile apps & webapp with implement visual design systems.
- Improve user experience and add new features to existing products.
- Assisting frontend developers with the design of HTML and CSS frameworks.

Niramoy Healthtech Limited

UI Designer (February 2020 - September 2021)

1 year 8 months

- Designed mobile app for patients.
- Creating a desktop prescription frontend using Bootstrap for doctors.
- Involving front-end designers in the design process.

SKILLS

UX							
•	User Centered Design	•	Problem Solving	•	Critical thinking	•	Information Architecture
•	Wireframe	•	Prototype	•	User Flow		
UI							
•	Visual Design	•	Material Design	•	Human Interface Guidelines	•	Design System
•	Typography	•	Color Theory	•	Responsive Design		

TOOLS

Figma
Adobe XD
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Photoshop

FRONTEND

HTML
CSS
Tailwind CSS
Bootstrap

EDUCATION

United International University

Bachelor of Science — Computer Science & Engineering (2014 – 2019)

PROJECTS

- Kookit <u>See details</u> | <u>Figma Link</u>
- Wearit Delivery System- See details | Figma Link
- Wearit eCommerce Mobile app See details | Figma Link
- Movee Movie Ticket Booking App See details
- Annual Performance Agreement (APA) Redesign(Govt. Project)
- Thkee Elearning system (NDA) Thkee is an Arab platform that provides expert and technician-led professional training courses in a variety of fields using advanced technologies.

MY PORTFOLIO

